翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
欢迎来到大家庭
Welcome to the family.
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
是啊 终于来了
Yeah, I'm finally in.
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
你妹妹是为了并购计划过来的
Your sister's just in for the day.
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
-是吗  -只是来观察观察
- Yeah? - Just to observe.
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
压制　Jason肖
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
瑞亚 我们接到她了
Rhea, we got her.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
这家人信任她
The family trusts her.
你要是能说服她 就意义重大了
You get her on board, that's huge.
我想要皮尔斯 但是 只有快点完成收购对我才有意义
I want Pierce, but it only works if we meet fast.
代表皮尔斯家族
On behalf of the Pierce family,
这条消息将是典型的和谐 微妙的表达方式
the message would be a typically balanced, nuanced,
想表明的态度是 "滚开"
and objective "fuck off."
-有枪手  -劳驾 劳驾
- Shooter! - Excuse me, excuse me.
-这是怎么回事  -我们只是想保证你的安全
- What's going on? - We just want to get you safe.
肯德尔在哪儿 他安全吗
Where's Kendall, is he safe?
泛美网络的栏目制片人 是自杀
ATN segment producer, it was a suicide.
我们确实有一件事要提
We did have one thing to mention.
240亿美元
Twenty-four billion dollars.
而且 我说话算话
And they can trust me.
我可不可以换到另一个部门去工作呢
Would it be okay for me to maybe go to another department?
别再往我身上扔了
Stop pelting me!
警卫
Security!
我们不会用你管理培训课程第一天
We are not building a ride that you came up with
想出来的点子建游乐设施的 罗曼
on your first day of management training, Roman.
技术上讲 我是你他妈的老板
Technically, I'm your fucking boss.
去睡觉 把你所有的点子都打飞机打出来
Go to bed and masturbate all your ideas out.
也许我会打飞机的
Maybe I will.
你这头恶心的小猪
You disgusting little pig.
你和爸爸之间到底他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck is going on between you and Dad?
-他给你提条件了吗   -不会是我当接班人的
- Did he make you an offer? - It's not gonna be me.
谢谢 理查德
Thanks, Richard.
嗨
Hi!
你好吗 你回来了 伦敦怎么样
How are you? You made it! How was London?
-很好 嗯  -是吗 你还好吗
- Good. Yeah. - Yeah? You okay?
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
在哪里...肯在这吗...
Where's... Is Ken here? Is...
-我不知道  -罗曼呢
- I don't know! - Is Rom?
我不知道 那...你还好吗 你都做了些什么事
I don't know. So, are... you okay? What did you do?
-你见到谁了  -嗯 这个说不清
- Who did you see? - Yeah, it was a blur.
-你还好吗  -我很好啊
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
我只是心里有事
I'm just preoccupied.
好的 但是你不觉得...
Okay. But you don't think that...
-什么  -你觉得他今天会不会...
- What? - You don't think it could be  today that he...
什么
What?
-可能宣布你接班  -不会
- Might announce you? - No.
但...
But...
是的 你知道 出发去皮尔斯集团之前
Yeah, you know, full family briefing pre-departure
全家简报 确实是...
to the Pierces', where...
宣布接班人的好时机 所以...
it would be smart to have someone to announce, so...
-是的  -是的
- Yes. - Yeah.
好的 好吧 那你为什么不说 亲爱的
Okay. Well, why didn't you say, honey?
因为也可能不是 所以 你可以放松点吗 这...
Because it probably isn't, so would you relax? It's...
我很放松 我只是很兴奋
I am relaxed. I'm just excited.
理查德 万岁 我辛勤的劳动者同事
Richard! Hail, my fellow toilerman.
我从真正的美国回来了
I have returned from real America,
带着洞察一切的天赋
bearing the gift of sight.
-你的暑期班怎么样  -什么意思
- How was summer camp? - What's that?
没听懂 我和我的同伴约翰尼·朗奇佩尔
Didn't catch that. I've been down in the salt mines so long
在盐矿里劳作太久了
with my fellow Johnny Lunchpails,
差点连话都不会说了
I no longer speak One-Percent.
罗曼 你只是在那扔糖苹果
Roman, you were slinging candy apples,
又不是去挖巴拿马运河
not digging the Panama Canal.
我见识了这个世界的真实面貌 西沃恩
I've seen the world for how it really is, Siobhan,
这改变了我 我现在是铲爆米花的工人
and it has changed me. I'm a kettle corn shoveler,
在这里向你展示像阴蒂一样充满皱褶的真相 嗨
here to show you frilly clit-flickers the truth. Hi!
老康
Con.
你这个有着金子般的心的老妓怎么样啊
How's the hooker with the heart of gold?
而且 你知道吗 我觉得这可能是个办法
And, you know, I think that could be a way in.
大家好 你们好 谢谢所有人....
Ho! Hello! Thanks, all....
车子已经在楼下等着了 但首先 我先宣布点事
Cars are waiting. But first, some announcements.
-弗兰克  -那 如大家所知
- Frank. - So, as you know,
好消息是皮尔斯对我们的出价很感兴趣
the good news is that the Pierces are entertaining
但是 坏消息是 他们正在调查
our offer, but, bad news, they're inquiring about
你的道德品质 就是这个周末
your moral character, hence this weekend.
他们都想直接面对面了解我们
They all wanna look us in the teeth.
对 他们想要我们的240亿 但是他们也想
Right. They want our 24 billion, but they also wanna be able
确保未来合并以后新闻媒体的完整性
to ensure the integrity of their news outlets - into the future.
我想要一个味道像他妈的桃子的洋葱 不过 无所谓了
And I want an onion to taste like a fucking peach, but there you go.
在我们浪费这个周末之前 我想先了解一下
Before we waste a weekend, can I just check
为什么这次会有所不同 爸爸
why this time is gonna be different, Dad?
缺乏读者群
Lack of readership.
PGM集团被左右包抄了
PGM is getting outflanked left and right.
整个大厦正摇摇欲坠
The whole edifice is crumbling.
嗯 那些只是尖叫声 "再见 再见 再见"
Well, that just screams, "Bye, bye, bye!"
我...我在开玩笑 我知道的
I... I'm kidding. I get it.
即使是南这个蜂后 也正在感受到外界的压力
Even Nan, the queen bee, is feeling the squeeze.
皮尔斯家族信托基金已经出现裂缝了
The Pierce Family Trust has fractured.
那 为了确保一切顺利
So, to ensure that everything goes smoothly,
我们为周末列了一些可以做和不可以做的注意事项
we have prepared a few do's and don'ts for the weekend.
那 什么 不可以在汤锅里拉屎吗
So, what, don't shit in the soup tureen?
要避开的话题 雷文黑德 泛美网络 以色列
Topics to stay clear of: Ravenhead, ATN, Israel,
"明亮的星"以及关于游艇的谣言
Brightstar, and Cruise's rumor mill.
把话题导向八卦 投资
Steer onto gossip, investments,
艺术 电影... 闲谈 更广泛的人文兴趣
art, movies... Tittle-tattle. Wider cultural interests.
那 如果更广泛的人文兴趣
Well, what if your wider cultural interest
是对着照片墙打飞机呢 我只是帮一个朋友问的
is hate-jerking to Instagram? Just asking for a friend.
我 她说的是我
Me! She's talking about me.
我想想还有什么 噢 最多喝两杯
What else? Two drinks maximum.
不要喝太多了
Not big drinkers.
没关系 这里没有任何人有明显的药物滥用问题
That's okay. Nobody here has any glaring substance abuse issues
以至于差点搞垮公司 对吧
that almost brought down the company, right?
汤姆 我们可能会不得不埋汰埋汰你 数落你的不是
Tom, we may have to shake you up a little, push you around a bit.
他们讨厌泛美网络 讨厌我们的报纸
They hate ATN, - they hate our papers.
你是承担泛美网络罪责的稻草人
You're the strawman for the sins of ATN.
会抽打抽打你 好吗
Cane your haunches a bit, okay?
好的 我们可以...我们能不能...也许...
Okay. Could we... Could we may... perhaps...
-把责任推到悉德头上  -不不不不
- Put the responsibility on Syd? - No, no, no, no.
我知道你什么意思 但是不行 我们...
I know what you're saying, but no. We...
我们得穿上刚毛衬衣[苦行者所穿的粗糙磨人的衣服]自省 把你称作人渣
We need to wear the hair shirt, call you a shitbag,
而且会说 我们从来不看泛美网络 懂了吗
and say that we never watch. Right?
好的 明白了 刚毛衬衣
Okay. Got it. Hair shirt.
瑞亚和我将引导大局
Rhea and I will handle the big picture.
再提醒我一下 瑞亚是在为公司工作吗
Remind me again, does Rhea work for the company?
提醒我们一下 你自己呢
Remind us, do you?
我只是在问 我们是不是真的想把
I'm just asking if we really wanna entrust
我们公司的命运寄托在另一家公司的总裁身上
the fate of our company to another company's CEO.
-我们可以信任瑞亚  -好的 我们不了解瑞亚
- We can trust Rhea. - Okay. We don't know Rhea.
-我了解瑞亚  -他妈的谁是瑞亚
- I know Rhea. - Who the fuck is Rhea?
-没错  -伙计们 爸爸的意思是
- Exactly. - Guys, what dad is saying is,
了解清楚自己的角色然后好好执行 好吗
just know your role and execute, okay?
好吧 我担心的是 肯德尔
Well, my worry is that Kendall
可能给人的感觉太酷 太可爱了
may come across as too cool and likable.
感谢大家的帮助
Thanks for all your help.
我们需要这个 拿下皮尔斯是我们代理权防御的关键
We need this. Bagging Pierce is the key to our proxy defense.
而防御就是生活本身 我们普利茅斯岩石见[位于波士顿东南部]
And the defense is life itself. See you at Plymouth Rock.
-你没事吧  -嗯 你晚一个小时出发
- You okay. - Yeah. An hour late,
到时候不要隐瞒你去了哪里
and make no secret where you've been.
-好的 没问题  -还有
- Yeah, we're good. - And,
这周末别碰毒品 好吗 危险人物
keep clean this weekend, killer?
理查德...
Richard...
-对不起 你先请 女士  -不 你先请
- Sorry about it. After you. My lady. - No, please.
是的 骑士精神还没有... 你懂的
Yep. Chivalry is not... You know.
-拉了屎才能铲  -那我当狗屎好了
- Shit before the shovel. - Allow me to be the shit.
-小可爱  -嗯
- Pinkie! - Yeah.
让他们处理下面那些食物链底层的家伙
Let them take care of the bottom-feeders.
-我们来对付南  -好的
- We work on Nan. - Okay.
-好警察 厌恶女人的警察那套吗  -是的 当然
- Good cop, misogynist cop? - Well, sure.
你知道的 女人的事嘛
You know, the woman thing?
-是的 嗯 是的  -他们喜欢你的政治观点
- Yeah. Well, yeah. - They like your politics.
好的 嗯
Okay. Yeah.
我知道你不喜欢这次并购
I know you don't like this buy.
不 不 我...你知道 我可以看懂其中的逻辑 是的
No, no, I... You know, I can see the logic. Yeah.
-应该是吧  -好 好
- I guess. - Good, good.
总之 很快就是我的产业了
Anyway, my baby soon.
继     承
第 二 季  第５集
那 怎么样了 你的培训课程
So, how's it going? The course?
这课程 实际上 我觉得 就是在胡说八道
It's actually, you know, I mean, it's bullshit,
但是 不错 是的
but it's good. Yeah.
我为你感到骄傲 儿子 上车吧
Well, I'm proud of you, son. Getting back in there.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thank you, Dad.
但是 这个周末 不要提培训的事
But this weekend, don't mention it.
听起来就像你去商业课程的幼儿园里回炉再造
Sounds like you're back in business kindergarten.
对 谢谢
Right. Thank you.
大家都保持笑容
Everybody smile.
-我在笑呢  -是啊 笑得不像是变态
- I am smiling. - Yeah, not like a pervert.
天啦 看看他妈的蓝爸爸[蓝精灵]
Jesus. Check out fucking Papa Smurf.
这他妈已经开始奇怪了
This is too fucking weird already.
圣方济各的阿西西[意大利罗曼天主教僧侣 创立了方济各修士会]
St. Francis of Assisi!
你准备好慈善大拍卖了吗
Are you ready for the rummage sale?
你把一群混蛋带到我这来了
You've brought me animals!
欢迎来到特恩海文 我们的山间之城
Welcome to Ternhaven, our city on the hill.
-南·皮尔斯  -很高兴见到你
- Nan Pierce. - Pleasure.
我想 这一刻你等待了
I suppose you've been waiting for this moment
很长一段时间了 对吧 贪吃蛇
for quite a while, haven't you, greedy-guts?
-好吧...  -逗你呢 逗逗你
- Well... - Teasing. Teasing!
好的 谢谢你邀请我们到你家
Well, thank you for inviting us to your home.
好吧 我想我们会很开心了解一下
Well, I think we're gonna have fun getting a look
你们全家人 不是吗
at all of you, won't we?
南 别闲扯了 咱们去吃点心吧
Nan, stop blabbing and let us at the canapés!
来吧 回家吧 信守诺言
Come, come homeward. Promises to keep,
在我们睡觉前还有很长的路要走
and miles to go before we sleep.
你好 很高兴认识你 我听说过很多关于你的事
Hello, lovely to meet you. I've heard a lot about you.
康纳 我是玛尔妮 非常高兴...很高兴认识
Connor, I'm Marnie. Very nice... Pleasure.
-欢迎  -很高兴见到你
- Welcome. - Nice to meet you.
加布里埃尔 很高兴见到你
Gabriel. Nice to meet you.
小西
Shiv.
-你好 爱德华多  -我们以前见过面
- Hello, Eduardo -  We've met before.
那 我们胜算如何
So, how are we looking?
有些什么问题
Issue?
娜奥米从马林郡飞来了 这是...
Naomi has flown in from Marin, which is...
一个不错的惊喜
a nice surprise.
这对我们的收购决定有什么影响呢
What does that do to the math, then?
她...她有说她的想法吗 这是什么意思
Does she... Does she have a share? What does it mean?
嗯 事情复杂化了
Well, it complicates it.
那 为什么没有人预先告诉我
So, why wasn't I prepared for this?
因为这他妈不是我的工作
Because it's not my fucking job?
-去问你的人  -那 怎么说
- And ask your people? - So?
这种事她通常袖手旁观
She usually sits these things out.
-她可以左右南的决定  -我们可以抛开南直接和她谈吗
- She has major juice with Nan. - Could we do it without Nan?
-玛尔妮  -嗯
- Marnie! - Yes?
你我去喝一杯马提尼 现在就去
You, me and a martini, now!
好啊
Yes!
阴茎猫[加拿大无毛猫]
Penis cat.
"这是胜利之酒"
"This wine is triumphant"?
不是吗
No?
"你的阴道在吹喇叭 "
"Your vagina trumpets."
这是 "我在真理中凯旋"
It's, "I triumph in the truth."
对 当然 真理 我喜欢这句话 真是很棒 对吧
Right, of course, truth. Love it. It's the best, right?
真理 他看起来很酷
Truth. He seems cool.
各位 我保证不会耽误大家很多的喝酒时间
Everyone. I promise not to interrupt your tipple for long,
不过 我想花一点点时间
but I just wanted to take a brief moment
欢迎诸位来到我们有趣的小房子
to welcome you to our funny little house
并且 希望我们的客人知道
and to let our guests know
你们喝的是汉克·皮尔斯的"撞坏保险杠"
that what you're drinking is Hank Pierce's Break Bumper!
撞坏保险杠
The Break Bumper!
配方仍然是 这一点没有人相信
The recipe is still, and no-one believes,
泰迪·罗斯福[美国第26任总统]的贴身男仆的私家秘方
from the wallet of Teddy Roosevelt's valet.
-干杯 各位 干杯  -干杯
- Cheers, everyone. Cheers. - Cheers.
欢迎
Welcome.
嗯 我现在正在攻读我的第二个博士学位...
Yeah, I'm actually getting my second PhD right now in...
布朗大学的非洲研究
Africana Studies from Brown.
那你会成为一个双料博士
So you'll be a double doctor?
这个嘛 第二个博士学位要难得多
Well, the second PhD is much harder.
五年绝对是严酷的挑战
Yeah, five years is an absolute gauntlet.
肯定的 但是想想
I'm sure. But just think, you know,
等你毕业了 你就不用浪费十二秒
once you're done, you won't have to waste the twelve seconds
在维基百科上查找一些内容了
it takes to look up something on Wikipedia.
不过 说真的
But seriously, though,
你知道吗 这样很棒 这是了不起的成就
you know, well done. It's quite an achievement.
嗯 谢谢
Yeah, thank you.
康纳·罗伊
Connor Roy!
-我是马克西姆·皮尔斯  -你好
- Maxim Pierce. - Hi.
你就是要当总统的人吧
The man who would be king?
爱荷华州的唐吉诃德 在民意投票中摇摆
Don Quixote of Iowa, tilting at straw polls!
是的 我的心态很开放 欢迎每个人
Yep. I've got a big old tent, and everyone's welcome.
-那 你从政吗  -算是 布鲁金斯学会[美国最有影响力的智库之一]
- So, are you in politics? - Sort of. Brookings Institute.
布鲁金斯 是的 当然 一个优秀的精英机构
Brookings! Yes, of course, a fine, elite establishment.
我没想到你会是粉丝
I didn't take you for a fan!
我还以为你大体上是
I thought you were on the whole
"废除美联储" "氟化物是毒药"
"abolish the federal reserve," "fluoride is poison,"
"尿在罐子里" 那一类人呢
"pissing in jars," end of things.
不 我实际上追求所有事情的自由和正义
No, I'm actually on the liberty and justice for all end of things,
只不过是不同的方式
but different strokes!
肯来了 直升机螺旋下来
Here comes Ken. Spiraling down.
罗曼 你还记得娜奥米吗
Rom, you remember Naomi?
是啊 没错 因为...因为那件事
Yeah, that's right! From the... From the thing.
-是的  -那件事
- Yeah. - The thing.
你打算通过电话订购
Where you tried to order my family's legacy
我们家族的遗产 就像美团外卖
over the phone, like an Uber Eats.
-当然  -这下吃到苦头了吧
- Of course. - Burn.
-你好吗  -就是那件事
- How are you? - That's the thing.
你知道吗 我不错 我很好
You know, I'm well. I'm very well.
我工作得非常努力 知道吗
I'm working real hard, you know.
-是吗  -是的 不 完全没受伤 真的
- Yeah? - Yeah, no. Not at all, really.
也许吧 谁知道呢
Maybe. Who knows.
他的意思是说 他真的很有激情
What he meant to say is that he's really passionate
保持面向客户的品牌的完整性
about maintaining the integrity of the customer-facing brands.
你的家庭很有意思
You have an interesting family.
嗯 我为我儿子的迟到而道歉
Yeah, I apologize for the lateness of my son.
-没事  -他一直在做志愿者
- Well. - He's been volunteering.
真的吗 真让人敬佩
Really? That's impressive.
他在收购战的紧要关头还有时间做志愿者吗
He has the time, even in the teeth of a takeover battle?
-嗯...  -他很有能力
- Well... - He's very capable.
他带宽很宽[可以理解为能力很强]
A lot of bandwidth.
有这样的带宽真是太棒了
It's wonderful to have such bandwidth,
尤其是那个事情之后...你知道的
after everything that... You know.
不 谢谢 我...
No, thank you, I'm...
罗莎 罗莎 和我们一起喝一杯
Rosa! Rosa, have a drink with us.
我得把晚饭做好 小姐
I have to finish the dinner, Miss.
不 我知道 不过就...就一杯 你可以休息一下的
No, I know, but just... Just one. You can take a break,
-不是吗  -但是晚餐还没做好
- can't you? - But dinner.
好吧...好吧 行 你从不犒劳自己
Well... All right. All right. You never treat yourself.
肯德尔
Kendall!
嗨 你来了 我们想你了 儿子
Hi! You made it! We missed you, son.
感谢 爸爸 是啊 我...也想你
Thanks, Dad. Yeah. I... missed you too.
你来应付彼得没问题吧
Are you all right for targeting Peter?
你知道的 把一根金条塞进他妈的喉咙里
You know, shove a bar of gold down his fucking throat?
-当然 可以 明白了  -好
- Yeah, sure. Got it. - Good.
请原谅我...正如我的家人
Pardon me... As my family knows
非常了解的那样 我...我不是高谈阔论的大师
only too well, I am... I ain't no master of the speechifying,
但我想...我想感谢皮尔斯一家
but I would... I would just like to thank the Pierces
感谢他们的热情好客...我们就像希腊人中的罗马人一样扎眼
for their hospitality.... Like Romans amongst you Greeks,
我相信你们会发现 我们家所有人 你们懂的 都是大老粗
I'm sure you find us all rather, you know, big, vulgar,
而且很喧闹
and boisterous.
我们...我们感谢你们的宽容
We... We appreciate your forbearance.
而且 你们知道 作为一个老新闻人
And, well, you know, as an old news man,
如果我...如果我不赞扬你们所有人对PGM集团的管理有方
I'd be remiss if I... if I didn't commend all of you
那就是我的疏忽了
for your stewardship of PGM,
因为无论我们持有
because wherever we are
什么样的政治立场 我们都同意
on the political spectrum, we can all agree,
即使是十年后的十年
for decade after decade,
你们的媒体对我们伟大的
your outlets have been essential
美利坚共和国的运作仍然至关重要
to the functioning of our grand republic.
-愿它们永葆影响力  -说得好
- Long may they so remain. - Hear, hear.
-说得好  -说得好
- Hear, hear. - Hear, hear.
他想干掉你们 在你们头上拉屎呢
He would like to kill and shit on you!
我喜欢这样的爸爸 我们的爸爸为什么不能是这样的爸爸呢
I like this Dad. Why couldn't this Dad be Dad?
你收拾得很整洁嘛
You clean up nice.
你还好吗
How are you?
我很好 挺好的
I'm good. Good.
你之前还好吗
How are you really?
你知道的
You know.
是的 我知道 我知道 很高兴见到你
Yeah, I know. I know. It's good to see you.
-我们会需要你的帮助  -"我们"
- We could use the help. - "We"?
你 他们 我们 无所谓
You, them, us. Whatever.
我觉得这很棒 当然一切都很顺利
I think it's great. Of course it's going well.
我的意思是 没有人惹南或者意外地搞死她的猫
I mean, no-one's fucked Nan or killed her cat by accident,
所以我觉得 我们做得很好
so I think we're doing pretty good.
-是的 我知道 我知道  -你见过那个人吗
- Yeah, I know, I know. - Have you seen that guy?
让开一下
Excuse me.
你他妈的对马克说了些什么
What the fuck did you say to Mark?
-竟然嘲笑他的博士学位  -那 只是个玩笑
- Making cracks about his PhD? - Well, it was a joke!
-他还笑了  -嗯 看上去他并不喜欢那个笑话
- He laughed. - Yeah, it seemed he did not enjoy that.
他赞成收购 小西 他很可靠
He's a yes, Shiv! He's solid!
你为什么还要去招惹他
Why are you even bothering with him?
-我们是不是忘了马克西姆  -谁在盯着马克西姆
- Have we lost sight of Maxim? - Who's on Maxim?
我 我只想说 如果他
Me, and I just have to say, if he contradicts
再反驳我的政治哲学
any more planks in my political philosophy,
我会在他的"撞断保险杠"[酒]里面撒尿
I'm gonna piss in his Break Bumper.
他倾向于"不卖"
He's leaning "no sale".
废话少说 搞清楚你的角色
Cut the horseshit, know your role.
-好的 爸爸  -还有 小西
- Yeah, Pa. - And, Shiv,
我想要你去负责南
I want you on Nan.
好的 爸爸 我们没必要搞得这么一板一眼的
Okay, Dad, we don't have to be so schematic.
罗慕路斯
Romulus.
你笑的时候 请保持和其他人
When you laugh, please do it at the same volume
一样的声量
as everyone else.
我们不是把你从鬣狗农场带过来的
We didn't get you from a hyena farm.
-谢谢 爸爸  -好消息是
- Thanks, Pop. - The good news is that Nan
南似乎已经想好该怎么花钱了
already seems to be spending the money in her head,
不过 她仍然可能被她的家人左右
but she can still be swayed by her family,
所以 每一个亲戚都很重要
so every cousin counts.
我认为玛尔妮可能倾向于"卖" 所以...
I think Marnie might be leaning "sell", so...
玛尔妮不是问题 现在 你们每个人
Marnie isn't a problem. Now, everybody,
都做好自己的分内事 谁在盯彼得
stay in your lanes. Who's on Peter?
嗯 我会搞定的 爸爸
Yeah, I got it, Dad.
你会搞定的 真是让我服了 别吹牛了
You got it? I'm so impressed. Shut up.
好的 谈话的时候稍微艺术点 好吗[林肯中心: 纽约最大的表演艺术中心]
Okay, a bit of Lincoln Center chat, okay?
他担心我们是野蛮人
He's worried that we're barbarians.
-还有娜奥米  -嗯
- And Naomi. - Yeah.
-搞定娜奥米  -收到
- Hit Naomi! - Got it.
好了 开始
Okay, onwards.
忍受不了马克西姆吗
Can't stand up to Maxim?
小塔 你会帮我吗
Tabs, you gonna help me on that?
-他就是个混蛋  -他"现在不赞成" 你的政策的哪一部分
- He's an asshole! - What part of your policy  was he "not right now"?
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
不 所有的一切他都不赞成 他根本不考虑
No, everything. He's dismissing.
-嗯 到目前为止干得不错  -非常感谢
- Well, nice work so far. - Merci beaucoup.
我很"兴奋"能和你的其他学生
I'm very excited to be getting top marks
一起取得高分
along with your other pupils.
太赞了
Bravo.
好啦
Stop!
现在...
Now...
一起感恩吧
Grace.
恐怕我们家已经变成一神论了
I'm afraid we've gone so Unitarian out here
我们已经放弃了可怜的耶稣
that we've given up on poor Jesus,
开始崇拜莎士比亚了
and we have started worshipping Shakespeare!
发言的权杖交给你了
Your scepter.
凡人的一生所能提供的...最纯洁的宝藏
The purest treasure... mortal time affords
就是清白的声誉
is spotless reputation.
从这个意义上说 人不过是镀金的壤土
That away, men are but gilded loam,
或彩绘的粘土
or painted clay.
我的荣誉是我的生命 两者合而为一
Mine honor is my life; both grow in one.
夺去我的荣誉 我的生命就会完结
Take honor from me, and my life is done.
请喝汤吧 各位
Soup's on, people.
刚刚的祝词太棒了
That was awesome.
-我是肯德尔  -我知道 我是娜奥米
- I'm Kendall. - I know. Naomi.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
那 你是....
So, are you, like, a...
女演员或者女诗人什么的吗
an actress or like a poetess?
或者其他的职业 因为刚刚的发言很学院派
Or something? Because that was pretty legit.
我志愿
I, volunteer
在米尔谷的一个戒毒治疗中心做义工
at a drug addiction treatment center in Mill Valley,
也在那里继续康复治疗
and I continue my recovery there as well.
那...那样很好 我...
That... That's great. I...
嗯 实际上我自己也在康复治疗
Yeah, I'm actually in recovery myself.
-我知道  -好吧
- I know. - Okay.
看来我不那么一尘不染的名声已经在外了
My not-so-spotless reputation precedes me.
不 我只是看得出来
No, I could just tell.
好吧 好的
Okay. Right.
我想同时出版三本小说和一本回忆录
I'd like to have three novels and a memoir going at once.
-这就像自然选择  -兄弟 我听到了
- It's like natural selection. - Brother, I hear that.
-你喜欢看书吗  -我吗 经常看 是的
- Are you a reader? - Me? Big time. Yeah.
你能推荐一些奥普拉没有推荐的书目吗
Can you recommend anything that Oprah isn't pushing?
-有什么新的小说吗  -对
- Any new fiction? - Right?
是的 当然 我可以....
Yeah, sure, I can....
我很喜欢"电动马戏团"[说唱专辑]
I rather enjoyed The Electric Circus.
电动马戏团
The Electric Circus.
-作者是谁  -你说什么 什么
- Who's the author? - What was that? What?
-作者是谁  -天哪
- Who's the author? - Gosh.
我想说...妈的 是谁来着 是...提摩西·利普顿
I wanna say... Shit. Who was it? It was... Timothy Lipton.
是关于什么的 罗曼
What's it about? Rom?
电动马戏团是讲什么的吗
What's The Electric Circus about?
是关于一个年轻人
It is about a young man
如何在世界上取得成功
making his way through the world,
除了两个不同的时间段
except in two different time periods.
有点类似于来回地切换...
It kind of switches back and forth between...
马戏团部分是一个 你知道 隐喻
The circus part is a, you know, metaphor.
隐喻什么
For what?
对于现代生活的焦虑 西沃恩
For the anxiety of modern life, Siobhan.
我在谷歌上看到这本书呢
I'm not seeing it on Google.
你是说这本书叫"电动马戏团"吗
You said it's called "The Electric Circus"?
是啊 我想...我的意思是 我靠 是不是叫电动马戏团来着
Yeah. I thou... I mean, shit. Is it The Electric Circus?
嗯 我记得书名叫做...
Well, I think it's called...
这一切都非常有趣 不过 我们先求同存异 好吗
That's all very interesting, but let's just agree to disagree, shall we?
当然
Sure!
嗯 那只是专家的分析
Well, that's just the sort of expert analysis.
我期待从一个双唇牢牢地粘在索罗斯奶嘴上的
I'd expect from a deep-state wonk with both lips
深度书呆子身上看到这一点
firmly glued to the Soros teat.
好吧 你不能不了解华府
Well, you can't change Washington
就期望着改变华府
without knowing Washington.
我的意思是 你能说出
I mean, can you name me
一个众议院商务委员会的成员的名字吗
one member of the House Commerce Committee?
是的 我想我知道一个
Yeah, I think I know one.
斐迪南·D·谁他妈在乎 众议员
Representative Ferdinand D. Who-Gives-A-Shit
来自伟大的"谁他妈也不在乎"州
from the great state of No-One-Fucking-Cares.
好吧 我心服口服 我的意思是 清理一些
Well, I'm convinced. I mean, clear some space
总统山的空间 伙计们
on Mount Rushmore, folks!
是的 是的 好吧...
Yeah, yeah, well...
我还以为你说的是破坏球[拆除建筑物的金属球]
I actually thought you said the wrecking ball.
我只是想说 我...
I just wanted to say, I'm...
你正在攻读的学业 博士学位 我觉得很棒
What you're doing, the PhDs, I think it's great.
-我很抱歉如果我...  - 不 不 你的笑话很受欢迎
- I'm sorry if I... - No, no! It was a hit,
非常明显很受欢迎
a very palpable hit!
我受得了开玩笑的
I can take a joke.
对 因为确实是个玩笑
Right. Because it was a joke.
当然
Of course.
你是不是很高兴退出政坛了 西沃恩
Are you pleased to be out of politics, Siobhan?
是的 我就像在克服令人讨厌的胃病一样克服它
Yes, I am. I'm getting over it like a nasty stomach bug.
这可能是一个肮脏的行业
It can be a dirty business.
被某个有线电视新闻巨头弄得更脏了
Made dirtier by a certain cable news behemoth.
好了 瑞亚 我们友好点吧
Come on, Rhea, let's play nice now.
我们可以在房间里讨论白人民族主义的大象 不是吗
We can discuss the white nationalist elephant in the room, can't we?
稍微打开一下它的后备箱看看
Tug on its trunk a bit?
我不参与运营
I'm not operationally involved.
拜托
Come on.
不 不 不 我让我的人全权负责他们分管的事情
No, no, no, I let my people do their own thing.
我的意思是 如果你...如果你想谈谈泛美网络 你知道吗
I mean, if you... If you wanna talk ATN, you know,
汤姆是罪魁祸首
Tom's the barbarian.
嗨 大家好 我是...右翼食人魔 随时为您效劳
Hi, hello, I'm the... right-wing ogre at your service.
不会吧 你连自己的新闻频道也不信吗
Really, you don't even believe your own stuff?
好吧 我一直想平衡韦斯达的投资组合...
Well, I've always wanted to balance Waystar's portfolio with...
和...民意...
with... voice...
-左翼的民意吗  -好吧 不 皮尔斯不是...
- From the left? - Well, no. Pierce isn't...
你们只管遵循事实 无论事实指向哪里 对吧
Your people just follow the truth, wherever it leads, right?
嗯 这个 你知道吗 我们的人只是黑客
Well, you know, our people are just hacks.
-但是我们喜欢他们  -不是吧
- But we like 'em. - Come on!
我的意思是 我想我们...我们的人
I mean, I guess our... our people
也在努力追寻真相 小西
try to follow the truth, too, Shiv.
你给了观众他们需要的东西 我们给了他们想要的东西
You give them what they need, we give them what they want.
我们很般配
We make a good match.
当然 对 不 爸爸...
Of course. Right. No, Dad...
我想我们 爸爸 只是想要一个更大的帐篷 一个更大的馅饼
I think we, Dad, just wants a bigger tent, a bigger pie.
这意味着更多的利润
It means more profit,
然后更多的投资
and then more investment.
所以 如果我反对被市场这只看不见的手摸来摸去
So, I suppose that just makes me a prim little matron,
我想 这只会让我被看作一个
if I object to being fumbled
一本正经的小主妇吧
by the invisible hand of the market?
那...那...不
Th... That's... No.
我不是那个意思 我...
That's not what I meant. I...
当然 公平交易并不是抢劫
Sure, a fair exchange isn't exactly robbery,
而且 据说金钱确实能让世界变得圆满 所以...
and money does allegedly make the world go round, so...
金钱 金钱是一种社会结构
Money? Money is a social construct,
而美德 正直
whereas virtue, integrity,
这些东西实际上是存在的
these things actually exist.
嗯 ...只是...好吧 因为就在今天早上
Well, the... Just... Well, because just this morning,
我去了商店 我买了一磅火腿
I went to the store, and I bought a pound of ham,
我是这样支付的 你知道吗
and I paid for it by, you know,
我告诉他们 我真的很担心环境[汤姆暗示 "正直"买不了火腿]
telling them I was really worried about the environment.
别介意汤姆 出于某种原因
Don't mind Tom, he finds other people's integrity
他认为别人的诚信是对他个人的冒犯
a personal affront, for some reason.
嗯 是的 那是...谢谢你 我就是一块烂泥
Well, yes, that's... Thank you, I'm a piece of dirt.
是的 是的 我接受了
Yep. Yep. I'll take it.
对
Right!
等一下 汤姆 汤姆 如果真的收购了
Wait a minute, but Tom, Tom, if there was an acquisition,
那么 作为新闻部门的负责人
then, as head of news,
你会成为掌控我们皇冠上的珠宝的人 对吧
you would be the guy in charge of our crown jewels, right?
好吧 这一点我们必须再看看
Well, we'd have to see about that.
听到了吗 汤姆
Hear that, Tom?
听起来不确定哦 要毛遂自荐下吗
Sounds dicey. Got a pitch?
汤姆 一切都取决于你要说的话
Tom, everything rests on what you're about to say.
放过他吧
Lay off him!
等一下 我没有听到答案
Wait a minute, though. I didn't hear.
那 他会继续担任新闻部门的负责人吗
So, would he stay on as the head of news?
-我...  -噢 可食用菜叶之王
- I... - King of edible leaves,
菠菜陛下
His Majesty, the spinach.
听着 我只是...我觉得...
Look, I just... I think there's...
商业 新闻价值...
The business, the journalistic values...
这个家里有很多你们的崇拜者 就是这样的
There's a lot of admirers in this family. That's all.
跟所有刚刚皈依的人一样 小西是一个狂热者
Like all recent converts, Shiv is a zealot.
我想我们都能达成共识的是
I think what we can all agree on is that
不管是什么样的立场 对于人们的沟通都是很好的
it's great for people to communicate, of whatever stripe.
我想 梭罗在电讯报上是这么说的
I think it was Thoreau who said of the telegraph,
"缅因州可能会和得克萨斯州对话 但是 如果他们之间
"Maine may speak to Texas, but what if they have nothing
没什么可说的呢"
to say to one another?"
这句话应该刻在世界上每一部iPhone手机外壳上
That should be engraved into the bezel of every iPhone in the world.
-说得好 刻在外壳上  -你和雪莉通过话吗
- Hear, hear! The bezel. - Have you spoken to Shirley?
我很抱...我们先失陪两分钟
I'm so sorr... Will you excuse us for two seconds?
-我很担心我们的...是...  -我们的狗 蒙代尔
- I'm so worried about our... It's a... - Our dog, Mondale.
是狗的事 真是蠢大了 对不起...
It's a dog thing. So silly. Sorry to...
它现在病得很重
Is very ill at the moment.
关节炎 我们觉得是关节炎
Arthritis. We think it's arthritis.
-非常抱歉  -他的臀部
- So sorry. - His hips.
请原谅我们 抱歉
Excuse us. Sorry.
他们有一只狗 一只叫蒙代尔的狗
They have a dog. A dog named Mondale.
很有用 对吧
That's helpful, right?
是啊 是的
Yeah, it is.
这就是...这就是发生的情况 给了你城堡的钥匙
This is... This is what happens. You get given the keys to the castle,
结果你瘫痪了 在那傻盯着眼镜蛇的眼睛
and then you get paralyzed, staring into the eyes of the cobra.
你在里面把我逼得太狠了
You're riding me pretty hard in there.
-你认为我应该多点反击吗  -你知道 然后
- You think I should fight back more? - You know, and then,
他感觉到了你的踌躇 然后他就是...
he smells the vacillation, and then he's just...
他吃定你了 你完了 他又搞定了一个柠檬
He's got you. You're done. He's juiced another lemon.
如果你也不再敲打我 那就太好了
It would be nice if you stopped beating up on me too.
-什么  - 也许你也可以
- What? - Maybe you could stop
-停止敲打我  -什么 什么啊...
- beating up on me too. - What? What do...
那什么都不是 那太傻了
That's just nothing. That's silly.
-什么...没人在乎  -从技术上讲 我很在乎
- What... No-one cares. - Well, technically, I care.
-我在乎  -好吧 有时你会说些蠢话
- I care. - Well, sometimes you say stupid things.
你知道吗 他让我反省自己了
You know, he's got me second-guessing myself.
我对达成交易的最佳策略犹豫不决 而且这交易我根本不喜欢
I'm wavering on the best strategy for landing a deal that I don't even like.
-我真的很想要这个  -我知道
- I really want this! - I know.
真的 我想坐在那张桌子旁
Really, I wanna be sitting at that table.
听我说
Listen to me.
你就是坐在桌子旁
You are sitting at the table.
你是
You are.
-是的  -好吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
我没事了 我们走吧
I'm good. Let's go.
他们打算领养小孩 你知道吗 那个排队清单
They're trying to adopt. You know, the list is,
有点 疯了 所以我在想 如果他们在六个月内
like, insane, so I'm thinking, like, if they can't have a baby
不能生孩子的话 我会 你知道吗 我会把我的子宫借给他们
in six months, I'm just gonna, you know, offer them my womb.
有何不可呢 我很年轻 我很坚强
Why not? I'm young, I'm hardy.
我有个朋友就这样做了 真是太棒了
I have a friend who did that. It was so great.
不过 希望不会太不礼貌 那你们两个呢
But if it's not too rude to ask, then what about you two?
你的意思是 我们生个孩子吗 不 我们没计划
You mean us having a baby? No, we're not planning
-生孩子 因为...  -挫死了
- to have a baby, because... - Oop.
生孩子需要我们做爱
That would require us having sex.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-我不是故意打探的  -乱说 你就是故意的
- I don't mean to pry. - Yes you did.
不不不不 这完全没问题 只是...
No, no, no, no. It's totally fine. That's just...
那就像不是我们的风格 这不是我们做的事
That's, like, not how we do it. It's not our thing.
我们有点像太监闺蜜
We're kind of like eunuch besties.
-好吧 我不会这么说  -这种关系适合我们
- Well, I wouldn't say that. - It works for us.
显然 这是个笑话 她在开玩笑 事实上
It's a joke, obviously. She's kidding. We're actually
我们在这方面相当无情 只有性爱
quite relentless in that regard. Just Fuck City.
噼啪你个隆叮咚
Bingo, bango, bongo.
话说 你没有孩子 对吧
Anyway, you don't have any kids, right?
精神焕发了[吸过了]
Refreshed?
是啊 是的 当然啦
Yeah. Yep, you bet.
玛西娅 那 请告诉我 你...你在贝鲁特长大的
Marcia, so, so tell me. You... You grew up in Beirut.
那里是什么样的
What was that like?
嗯 她...她真的不喜欢谈论这个
Well, she... She doesn't really like to talk about it.
也许是你不想问这个
Or you don't like to ask about it.
嗯...当我们第一次见面时 第一个还是第二个晚上
Well... when we first met, the first or second night,
我们彻夜未眠...
we stayed up all night...
她告诉了我 她的整个人生故事
And she told me her whole life story.
如果我有一年时间 我是不会告诉你我的一生的
If I had a year, I couldn't tell you my whole life.
-好吧  -有意思
- Fine. - Interesting.
给你们俩都再倒一杯吧
Another glass for both of you?
这个 嗯 我们一般不...
Well, now, we tend to kind of keep it to...
好的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
你说什么
Excuse me?
他的酒窖都是新世界的红酒 不适合我
His cellar is all New World, and it doesn't suit me.
好吧 你为什么不说
Well, why didn't you say?
它适合你 所以能够适合我 看到没 我不是个苛刻的人
It suits you, so it can suit me. See? I'm not a difficult person.
好吧 既然我们还在闲聊
Well, as long as the fat is being chewed,
我想我就不能不提 你们自己也是
I suppose I would be remiss not to mention that you're being targeted
被收购的目标 对吧
for acquisition yourself, correct?
那 嗯 那是...
That. Well, that's...
你知道的 那个已经结束了
You know, that's all over.
-好吧 唉  -桑迪身体不太好
- Well, alas. - Sandy's not well.
梅毒 简直不敢相信
Syphilis, if you can believe it.
我...是的 我从没...
I... Yeah. I never...
我从一开始就不相信
I never believed that the takeover bid
-收购要约是真的  -波将金式掠夺[故弄玄虚]
- was real to begin with. - A Potemkin pillage.
听着 我必须得问问 内部分歧的问题
Look, I have to ask. The internal differences.
-都抚平了吗  -相当平
- Have they been smoothed over? - Very much so.
你有没有想过 把钥匙交给谁[谁做接班人]
And any thought given to whom you might hand over the keys?
噢 女士 这问题太过了
Why, Madam, that is very forward.
你一点也不好玩
And you're no fun.
我们现在都是朋友了 不是吗
We're all friends here now, aren't we?
好吧...
Well...
格丽是名义上的总负责 这是权宜之计
Gerri is on the paperwork as a stopgap,
但是 即使是她自己 也会第一个承认无法胜任这份工作
but even she'd be the first to admit that she couldn't really do the job.
好吧 也许是第二个承认
Well, maybe the second to admit.
有一个名字
There is a name.
但是 你知道的 我真的不喜欢假设
But, you know, I really don't like to deal in hypotheticals.
他是个谜
He's an enigma.
-好吧 有一天我会宣布的  -真是心痒痒啊 伙计们
- Well, one day. - What a tease, folks.
-就单独在我耳边悄悄说  -你知道吗 那样的话 我会开始觉得
- Just whisper it in my ear. - You know, I'll start to think
没人需要我了
I'm not wanted.
只是...你可以...
Just... You can...
嗯 你知道...
Well, you know...
看在他妈的上天份上 爸爸 告诉他们会是我
For fuck's sake, Dad, just tell them it's gonna be me.
-是这样吗  -就是这样
- Is that so? - That is so.
-罗曼 发生了什么事   -我的生命刚刚结束了
- Roman, what's happening? - My life just ended.
是讨论过 但我认为 我们并不完全
It's been discussed, but I don't think we're quite
-在这个时候...  -不 不会很快接班
- at the point where... - No, not any time soon.
我们...我们已经讨论过交接过渡
We've... We've discussed the transition
-和一些安排  -我们不想拿这事来烦你
- and some arrangements. - We won't bore you.
没有 但是我觉得 我们可以告诉大家
No! But I thought we could tell you all, though,
以朋友的身份
as friends.
是啊 你知道吗 也许是这顿晚餐
Yeah. You know, maybe this dinner
上得有点早了
was a little bit premature.
看上去你们家有些事情还在琢磨
Seems like you guys are still working some things out.
不 不 彼得 别担心 这只是家里人瞎闹呢
No, no, Peter, don't worry, this is just family hijinks,
-和往常一样 我们很好的  -真的吗
- as usual. We're good. - Is that true?
你能住嘴吗
Will you stop?
好吧 无论如何 我...我只是在想
Well, anyway, I... I was just thinking,
这是一个如此美丽 晴朗的夜晚....
it is such a beautiful, clear night out....
马克...
Mark...
-马克  - 我说了"哈"
- Mark? - I said, "ha".
你能给我们介绍一下饭后的观星活动吗
Would you like to guide us on a little after-dinner stargaze?
遥望星空 我很乐意向你们展示一下我们这片小小的天空
Stargaze? I would love to show you our little corner of the sky.
非常棒
Marvelous.
给每个人都准备了靴子 不用担心
Boots for everyone, not to worry.
-你知道这事吗  -不 不 我不知道
- Did you know? - No. No, I did not know.
我们走吗
Shall we?
请记住 我是1989年获得的哥伦比亚大学博士学位
Keep in mind that I got my PhD at Columbia in '89,
所以我不是惠特曼所说的"学识渊博的天文学家"
so I'm not what Whitman would call a "learned astronomer."
对吧 不 但是...所以 我希望我能向你们展示...
Right? No, but... So, I wish I could show you through...
通过望远镜 但是我们的裸眼...
Through a telescope, but our naked eyes...
-玩得开心吗  -当然
- Having fun? - Sure.
-我乐在其中  -我也是
- I am having fun. - Me too.
-你也是吗  -看着你们的人崩溃
- You too? - Watching you people melt down
是地球上最令人心旷神怡的活动了
is the most deeply satisfying activity on planet Earth.
是吗
Yeah?
-谢谢  -当然 没问题
- Thank you. - Sure. You got it.
我们...我们的目标就是取悦你们
We... We aim to please.
不 我...感觉自己很多余
No, I... feel quite redundant.
我的意思是 我是来这里搞砸交易的 但是...
I mean, I came here to fuck any deal, but...
看起来你们自己就搞砸了 所以...
it seems you all have just fucked it yourselves, so...
所以...
So...
你会问我吗
are you gonna ask me?
问你什么
Ask you what?
你想跟我来一点非法毒品吗
Would you like to do some illegal drugs with me?
-是的 我想  -很好 走这边
- Yes, I would. - Good. This way.
好吧 晚安
Okay, goodnight.
真他妈鸡巴操蛋
Jeepers-fucking-creepers,
什么狗屎啊 那就像...
what a shit-piñata. That was like...
那是我见过的最典型的罗伊的事情了
That was like the most Roy thing I have ever seen.
就像我把一夸脱的罗伊注入我的眼球
It's like I got a quart of Roy injected into my eyeballs.
-有酒吗  -你在开玩笑吗
- Is there booze? - Are you kidding?
没有 只有艾米丽·迪金森的诗集和低密纺织的床单
No, it's just Emily Dickinson and low-thread-count sheets.
小西 那...
Shiv, what...
那到底是怎么回事 解释一下你为什么那样出招
What even was that? Explain the chess move.
我...我不知道 我只是...我只是...我只是他妈的脱口而出了
I... I don't know. I just... I just... I just fucking said it.
-你只是脱口而出吗 没有计划过吗  -不 不是真的 我...
- You just said it? No plan? - No, not really. I...
我估计我当时想 你知道的 "去他妈的
I guess I thought, you know, "Fuck him.
去他妈的 他把我骗了"
Fuck him for stringing me along!"
只是 你懂的 要么拉屎要么别占坑
Just, you know, shit or get off the pot.
对 对
Right. Right?
但是 你知道 我想我并没有真正想到...
But, you know, I guess I didn't really think that so much as...
因为 你知道 只是...老天 我的头
As, you know, just... Jesus Christ, my head.
因为我不确定 如果我和你没有任何关系
Because I'm not sure how much love there is for me
我还能得到多少的宠信
in a... as a sort of independent-of-you
你懂吗
sort of person. You know?
是的 我爸爸真的不喜欢被人逼迫
Yeah, my dad doesn't really like to be pushed.
-不喜欢  -不 所以可能会产生影响
- No. - No, so there could be repercussions.
-比如呢  -嗯 比如...
- Like what? - Yeah, like...
我不知道 比如...
I don't know, just like...
比如 我完蛋了
Like if, I've fucked it.
你完蛋了吗
You've fucked it?
对
Right.
我以前是个疯子
I used to be a maniac.
像一头野兽 但是...现在对我来说情况不同了
A beast, but... It's a different situation for me now.
对
Right.
-你应该听听你自己的话  -去你的
- You should hear yourself. - Screw you.
-好啊  -好吗
- Yeah. - Okay?
但是层次不同
But there are levels.
当然 不 是的 嗯 我的意思是 我基本上是
Sure. No, it's true. Yeah, I mean, I was basically
一个吊线木偶
hanging by a fucking thread.
我熬过来了 你知道吗
I'm coming through, you know?
就像 我重新振作了
Like, I'm getting it together.
嗯 我也是
Yeah, me too.
我知道听起来不像那么回事 但...
I know how that sounds, but...
是真的
it's true.
-我甚至不能...  -那些星星太棒了
- I can't even... - Those stars were amazing.
现在他妈的甚至不能刷牙
Can't even brush my fucking teeth now.
你给我带来了一个非常有趣的周末
Such a fun weekend you brought me on.
我是傻子吗 我是一个他妈的白痴吗 我是傻子吗
Well. Am I stupid? Am I a fucking idiot? Am I stupid?
-罗  -嗯
- Ro? - Yeah.
我...我星期一要开会
I... I have a meeting on Monday.
你知道吗 我...我真的想
You know? And so I'd just, like... I really wanna
处理你所有的发神经 和你谈谈发生的一切
deal with all your neuroses and talk about it and everything,
但是 如果你要发疯的话...
but if you're gonna get kind of crazy...
我可能得去看看娜奥米
I might just see if Naomi
能不能让我去她的床上睡觉了
would let me, you know, crash in her bed.
-好吧 我们搞吧  -嗯 没问题
- All right. Let's fuck. - Yeah, totally.
我们做得很"棒" 所以 这点子不错
We do the sex so well, so, that's a great idea.
好的 来吧 过来这里 你这个火辣的小婊子
All right, come on. Come here, you hot fucking piece of shit.
好的 好的 慢点
Okay, okay, easy!
-慢点 狼人  -对不起
- Easy there, wolfman. - Sorry.
-天啦  -这太棒了
- Jesus! - That was awesome.
-我太擅长这个了  -老天
- I'm so fucking good at this. - Christ!
抱歉
Sorry.
-就像...  -我知道
- It just was like... - I know.
真的用手指使劲捏
Really squeezing hard with your finger.
这真的很性感
It was really sexy.
我搞你的方式
How I just took you.
那很棒 你...你想要吗 我们可以...
That was great. Do you... Do you wanna, though? Can we...
你想不想要
Do you wanna?
-好的  -嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
-我想...和我做爱吗  -不
- Do I want to... make love with me? - No.
我不是...
I'm not...
我没有对解决你不感兴趣
I'm not uninterested in solving you.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yes.
你觉得我们有办法那个 比如...
Do you think there's a way that we can, like...
做点小错事吗
make it kinda like wrong?
直升机哟
Chopper ahoy.
我操
Shit!
让我看看你有什么真本事
Show me what you got!
好吧
Okay.
高度计打开 摇摆...摇摆棍 手柄就位
Altimeter is go. Wiggle... Wiggle stick, twisty stick is go.
油门...
The throttle...
涡轮增压 我们得把这个戴上
Turbo throttles. We gotta put these on.
旋转旋转 小鸡叫唤
Spinny-spinny, chicken dinny!
你根本不知道自己在干什么
You don't know what you're doing!
卧了个槽
Holy fuck!
等等
Wait.
不
No.
不 不 停机
No, no! Abort!
停掉 停掉 停掉 把飞机停掉
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off.
我们很好 我很好 我们没事 我们没事的
We're good. I'm good. We're okay. We're okay.
好了
Yeah.
我们很好 非常好
We're good. That's good.
这只是一个小小的技术问题
There's just a slight technical issue
我喜欢称之为晕转器[口误]
with what I like to call the spriller.
-旋转器吧  -旋转器
- The spinner? - The spinner.
你真是个无足轻重的小人物 不是吗
You're such a little nothing, aren't you?
也许吧
Maybe.
我不...我只是...我只是想开灯
I don't... I'm just... I'm just gonna put the light on.
不要...好了 我希望你没有开灯 那样...
Don't... Okay, I wish you didn't do that. That's...
我知道 我只是...我需要 那个...
I know, I just... I'm a person who needs, like...
-小塔 你应该扮死鱼的  -视觉刺激
- Tabs, you're meant to be dead. - Visual stimulation
-来进入状态 所以...  -我知道 我明白了 但我...
- to get into it, so... - I know, I get that, but I...
这对我们有帮助 我向你保证
That will help us, I promise you.
那我的需要怎么办 但是不要...
What about my needs? But don't...
当然 我想我们可以尝试一下 你可以
Sure. I thought we could just, like, try. You could just
-闭上眼睛...  -是的 但是你不应该
- keep your eyes closed... - Yeah, but you shouldn't be
兴奋 因为死了的女人下面是干的
turned on, because dead women aren't wet.
对 好吧...
Right, okay...
-有点破坏了现实主义  -那...让我...
- Kinda ruining the realism. - So... Let me just...
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
你希望这看起来像是我已经死了
You want it to seem like I'm dead,
-而你在强奸我  -我不想陷入
- and you're raping me? - I don't want to get into
语义上的争论 ...我的老天 不 这会有点像
a semantic arg... My God, no. It's just gonna be a little less
"性爱 好棒哦 "
like, "Sex, yay!"
是的 我...我...
Yeah, I... I...
我想也许今晚太平间正在关闭
I think maybe the morgue is closing for the night.
好的 只是 我...我只是说 如果我们
Okay. It's just, I'm... I'm just saying, if we, like,
礼貌地同意一件错误的事情 那它就不再是错误的了
politely agree on a wrong thing, then it's no longer wrong.
我的意思是 我...那就像基本的勃起算术一样
I mean, I'm... That's just like basic boner arithmetic.
我只是...是的 不 谢谢你上的这一课
I just... Yeah, no, thank you for that lesson,
"不能做爱"教授 我...我要进里面去了
Professor Can't-Fuck. I'm... I'm gonna go in here,
还有 你懂的 如果你听到我的电动牙刷响的时间
and, you know, if you hear my electric toothbrush
有点太长了 那是因为我在自慰 所以...
for a little too long, it's because I'm masturbating, so...
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
当我发生我最大那次...
When I had my, big...
我...最大那次交通意外的时候...
My... biggest crackup...
我妈妈死了
My mom died.
我无法从南非来到这里
And I couldn't get from South Africa to this,
而你们的人 还有你们他妈的小报
and you people and your fucking tabloids
就一直 报道这事 宣传这事
just, like, all the time pushing it and selling it,
直到我搞了个高潮...
until I put a cherry on top and...
我...把我他妈的奥迪裹起来放在高速公路的分隔线上
I... wrapped my fucking Audi around a highway divider.
所以 是的 操你妈的 操你们全家
So, yeah. Fuck you. Fuck your people,
操你妈的和平烟斗[北美印第安人用来表示和睦]
and fuck your peace pipe.
你知道最有趣的是什么吗
You know what the funny thing is, though?
是我的手腕永远不能完全愈合吗
That my wrist will never fully heal?
还是外面流传有我躺在血泊里 股骨戳出来的
Or there's photos of me caked in blood with my femur
-照片  -我们都有自己的不堪 对吧
- poking out? - We all have something, right?
这笔交易不会改变这一切
This deal isn't gonna change all that.
-我的意思是 我只想说...  -你把一切都安排好了
- I mean, all I would say is... - You've got it all sorted.
不要阻止你自己逃跑
Don't block your own escape.
想象一下 摆脱这一切
Just imagine getting out from under all this.
对吧 你可以拿钱...
Right? You can take the money...
你他妈可以离开这里远走高飞
and you can just get the fuck out.
然后呢
And then what?
然后 你就自由了
Then, you're free.
嘘
Psst!
-嗨  -天哪
- Hi. - Good God.
我希望我们可以谈谈我整个
I was hoping we could touch base about my entire future
被阻隔的未来 未来的罗曼性
being Hindenburged. The Romanity.
要么进来 要么滚开 别他妈在这闲荡
Come in or fuck off. This is loitering.
你知道 我又不像ATM那样一天24小时都在工作
You know, I'm not available 24 hours a day like an ATM.
-你之前知道小西的事情吗  -不知道
- Did you know about Shiv? - No.
我的意思是 不是那种告诉我的知道 但是...
I mean, I didn't know-know, but...
任何人只要不是他妈的白痴都会明白的
Anybody who wasn't a fucking moron would've figured it out.
是的 明白了 你有酒吗
Yeah, got it. Do you have any booze.
拿去
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢 如果你有任何....
Thanks. If you have any....
关于我今后应该做些什么的建议
suggestions for what I should do for the rest of my life,
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
好吧 我从培训计划那边收到了很好的报告
Well, I'm getting great reports from the training program.
不是吧 棒呆了 棒 我操 培训计划
No shit! Amazing! Yes! Fuck yeah! Training program!
也许有一天 我可以负责制造
Maybe one day, I can be in charge of making
过山车去...
the rolly-coaster go...
好吧 喝光 因为 你知道的 该睡觉了
Alright, drink up because, you know, it's bedtime.
-你快走吧  -好的
- Let's go. - Okay.!
除非您想安排一次我们之间的特别电话会议
Unless you wanna schedule one of our special conference calls
比如 现在
for, say, right now?
-你说什么  -嗨
- Excuse me? - Hi.
-等等 你是为这来的吗  -不 我不知道 也许 我不知道 不是
- Wait, is that why you're here? . - No. I don't know. Maybe. I don't know. No.
老天
Jesus Christ.
罗曼 这完全不能接受
Roman, this is unacceptable.
这样完全不合适
This is completely inappropriate.
-是吗  -你的家里人会怎么说
- Yeah? - What would your family say
要是他们知道你在我这里
if they knew you were here?
好吧 关我家人毛事
Well, my family jimmy-fuck-corn,
-而且 我不在乎  -是的 但你确实在乎
- and I don't care. - Yeah, but you do care.
-不  -是的 我知道你在乎
- No. - Yeah, I know you do.
他们会为你感到羞耻 而且理当如此
And they would be ashamed of you, and rightly so.
好的 我很抱歉 格丽 你...
Okay, I'm very sorry, Gerri how are you...
不 你没资格说话
No, you don't get to speak.
你总是很让人失望
You have always been a disappointment,
但这样就太...你已经越界了
but this is just... You have gone beyond the pale.
-我越界了吗  -是的
- I have? - Yeah.
你知道你是什么吗
You know what you are?
我是什么
What am I?
你是个变态的混蛋 你是一个变态的恶心禽兽
You're a sick fuck. You're a sick fucking animal.
-是吗  -是的 不要看着我
- Yeah? - Yeah, don't look at me.
进那间卫生间里去 快点
Get in that bathroom. Now!
进去
Go on.
你给我老实呆在里面
And you will stay in there
直到你自己把该做的事情做了[打飞机]
until you have done something with yourself.
你有毛病 罗曼
You have a problem, Roman.
你脑子里有个恶心的毛病
A revolting problem in your head.
这就是为什么你永远只是个耻辱
This is why you'll never be anything but a disgrace,
一个烂掉的小人物 天啦
a rotten little nothing. Jesus Christ,
你就是个经典的混蛋 罗曼
you are a classic fuckup, Roman.
我们该拿你怎么办
What are we gonna do about you?
如果他们现在看到你怎么办
What if they could see you now?
天哪
My God.
那 有人...昨晚有人玩得开心吗 还是...
So did anybody... Anybody get into any fun last night, or...?
好玩吗
Fun?
我昨晚在格丽的卫生间里打了飞机
I jerked off in Gerri's bathroom last night.
-你真有品味  -早上好
- So classy of you. - Morning.
没关系 别担心 这实际上是她的想法
It's okay. Don't worry about it. It was actually her idea.
我想 那真的让这个老女人洪水泛滥了
Think it really got the old gal's juices flowing.
就算是笑话 也是个令人倒胃口的想法
Even as a joke, that is a stomach-turning thought.
关于那家人的动态 我认为他想成为接班人
About the family dynamic of, I think he wants to be successor.
老康 我只是在清点人数
Con. I was just getting a headcount.
马克西姆炸了吗
Did it blow up with Maxim?
有点 但是后来 我们开了一瓶酒...
A little. But then we cracked open a bottle of port...
-而且 我...我不确定  -发生什么了
- and, I... I'm not sure. - What happened?
我喝醉了 承诺让他当国务卿
I got tipsy and I offered him the State Department?
-好事吗  -是的
- Good? - Yeah.
好
Good.
所以 这家人今天早上举行了闭门会议
So, the family had a closed-door meeting this morning.
-不好还是好  -我很抱歉 但...
- Bad or good? - I'm sorry, but...
我对此也一无所知 你知道 我...
I'm blind on this one too. You know, I...
我以为你会有更多的时间
I thought you'd have more time,
而且我以为我可以进去摇一摇那把旧螺丝刀[此处指的是南]
and I thought I could get in and waggle the old screwdriver,
但是 她并不总是听我的
but, she doesn't always listen to me.
-所以呢  -但是 南想在早餐后见见
- So? - But Nan would like to meet
你 玛西娅 格丽 小西 肯德尔
you, Marcia, Gerri, Shiv, Kendall after breakfast.
放松 不是生就是死
Relax. It's only life or death.
请坐
Please, take a seat.
玛西娅来了吗
Is Marcia coming?
她去散步了
She's gone for a walk.
她真是值得称赞 你圈子里很多男人
She is a credit. A lot of men in your station,
他们都追求 这样...类型的女人
they go for, a certain... type.
总之 我们都设法度过了一个
Anyway, we all managed to get through an evening
很愉快的夜晚 不过 我们来这里不是为了这个 对吧
pleasantly enough. That's not why we're here, is it?
是的 不是为了这个
No, it's not.
我对洛根·罗伊不抱任何幻想
I have no illusions about who Logan Roy is.
对他的孩子也是 我不是白痴
Who his children are. I'm not an idiot.
不过 我必须要做点什么
Well, something has to be done.
连续八个季度亏损是一个残酷的事实
Eight straight quarters of losses is a hard truth,
没有雄厚的财力 我们就没办法做好新闻
and we can't do good news without deep pockets.
你可以说我是一个浪漫的人 但是 我恰好相信
Call me a romantic, but I happen to believe that the presence
皮尔斯的新闻摄像机的出现是阻止东德边境守卫
of Pierce news cameras was what stopped certain East German
在1989年开枪的原因
border guards from opening fire in 1989.
我们帮助拆除了那堵墙[柏林墙]
We helped take down that wall.
是的
Yes.
难能可贵
Commendable.
你可能不相信 但我相信
You may not believe that, but I do.
现在 我们言归正传
Now, here we are.
一方面 我不太喜欢你
On the one hand, I do not like you very much.
而且我不喜欢你的政治立场
And I do not like your politics.
另一方面 今天早上我和我的表妹
On the other hand, I had a conversation this morning
娜奥米有过一次谈话 她相信
with my cousin Naomi, and she believes that a sale
出售是确保皮尔斯媒体蓬勃发展的唯一途径
is the only way to ensure that Pierce Media can flourish.
这可能就是我们现在的处境
And that may be where we are.
瑞亚 你怎么看
Rhea, what do you think?
我觉得...我觉得我们值更高的价钱
I think... I think we're worth more.
就市场估值而言
We have made a very generous offer
我们提出的报价已经非常慷慨了
in terms of market valuations.
-虽然如此  -我不喜欢被压榨
- Nevertheless. - I don't like to be squeezed.
我还以为我们已经谈好了价钱
I thought we had a number.
是啊 我的意思是...
Yeah. And, I mean...
我可以出到250亿
I could go to 25.
但是 必须很快完成交易
But it would have to be fast.
那 这样的话...带着一种沉重的心情
Then, in that case... with a certain heaviness of heart,
如果我真的不得不说 从家庭的角度来看...
if I honestly had to say, from the family's point of view...
同意
yes.
很好 如果我们能消除我们的道德顾虑
Very well. If we can clear up our ethical concerns,
我想我们可以谈
I think we can talk.
我们想保留一些董事会席位
We would like to retain some board seats,
并采取严格的编辑保护措施
and get ironclad editorial protections in place.
我觉得这可以敲定
I think that could be hammered out.
-还有  -还有
- Also. - Also.
我想我们还想谈谈管理层方面的问题
I think we would also like to have a conversation about management.
我不会同意让那个人监管我们的新闻[指汤姆]
I won't have that man overseeing our news.
对不起 这样是不行的
I'm sorry. It's just not tenable.
这不是问题
That won't be a problem.
更重要的是 我们希望你公开宣布接班人
More important, we would like you to publicly announce a successor.
我们希望 你公开宣布的这个人
And we would like the person you publicly announce
是西沃恩·罗伊
to be Siobhan Roy.
这...
Well...
这不是我做事的方式
that's not quite how I do things.
好吧 只能这样 要么就没有交易
Well, it will have to be, or there's no deal.
我们想同时宣布并购和小西接班的消息
We want to announce the sale and Shiv at the same time,
因为 坦率地说 虽然她是你们家的一员 但她很年轻
because, frankly, she may be one of you, but she's young,
她是一个女性 她的政治与核心价值观更合适
she's a woman, and her politics fit better with the core values
我们的家族企业 所以...
of our family business. So...
这是我的还价
that's the offer.
嗯 公平地说 你没有还价
Well, to be fair, you don't have an offer.
我有还价
I have an offer.
如果我要宣布我的女儿接班
And if I announce my daughter,
我会按照我的时间来宣布
my daughter will be announced on my time.
好吧 我来解释一下
Okay. Let me explain something.
-请啊  -你不能给我们所做的事情
- Please. - You can't put a value
估值
on what we do.
有意思 我确实给你们做的事情估值了
Funny. I have put a value on what you do.
好吧 如果你不让步 那恐怕我们就没有交易了
Well, if you won't budge, then I'm afraid we have no deal.
那就这样了
Then we're done.
你想听听我最喜欢的莎士比亚的台词吗
Would you like to hear my favorite passage from Shakespeare?
拿他妈的钱
Take the fucking money.
真是个奇怪的家族
What a weird family.
所以 你想谈谈吗
So, you wanna talk about it?
-你想说点什么 好啊  -怎么回事
- You wanna say something, fine. - What happened?
天啦 爸爸
Jesus Christ, Dad!
-怎么了  -这很危险
- What? - It's dangerous!
-没事吧  -只管开你他妈的旋风鸟
- We good? - Drive your fucking whirly-bird!
是吗 嗯
Yeah? Yeah.
这他妈的太对了
That's god-damn fucking right!
-我们应该走吗  -嗯 他不会说的
- Should we go? - Yeah. He won't talk.
我们再喝一杯就离开这里
Let's have one more and we'll get out of here.
理查德
Richard.
天哪
My God!
你们 你...你们成功了 那...是的 恭喜啊
You guys! You g... You did it! That... Yeah, congratulations!
你好 格雷格
Hello, Greg.
实际上现在叫格雷戈里了 不过...嗯
Actually going by Gregory, now, but... yeah.
无所谓啦 谢谢你 理查德
No matter. Thank you, Richard.
-你好 玛西娅  -好的 谢谢
- How are you, Marcia? - Good, thanks.
怎么...怎么样  怎么...很棒 还是...
And how... How was it? How wa... Was it awesome, or...?
嗯 很多变故
Yeah, it was eventful.
嗯 很好 挺好的
Yeah, it was good. It was good.
很高兴你过来 伙计
Nice of you to come by, man.
没什么  这对我们来说太重大了
No worries. This is huge for us!
把我们从被人收购的命运中拯救了
And this, like, saves us, maybe, from the takeover.
-格雷格   -格雷戈里
- Greg! - Gregory!
喝一杯 喝一杯 你这只美丽的伊卡博德仙鹤
Have a drink, have a drink, you beautiful Ichabod Crane!
-你这混小子   -是的
- Fuck you! - Yeah!
好吧 我...我得说 干得真漂亮  你赢了
Well, I j... I gotta say, well done. You won.
是啊 是啊  钱赢了
Yeah. Yeah. Money wins.
-敬我们自己   -敬我们自己
- Here's to us. - To us.
-敬我们自己  -敬我们自己
- To us. - To us.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠